worlddegrees.com 2014-10-08

# Privacy Policy | FutureStudents

Future Students Pty Ltd (ABN 35 136 749 436) (“Future Students”, “we”, “us” and “our”) provides advertisers (“Advertisers”) targeted advertising services and facilitates the delivery of advertisements to consumers viewing website(s) across the Internet (the “Advertisement(s)”). This privacy policy describes Future Students’ information-handling practices as they pertain to (i) visitors to our website located at [www.futurestudents.com](http://www.futurestudents.com/) (the “Site”), (ii) our dealings with our customers, and (iii) our targeted advertising services (the “Services”).

## 1\. THE SITE AND OUR DEALINGS WITH CUSTOMERS

###### Information Collected via the Site

The Site is intended primarily to offer information about Future Students and the services we provide.

We may collect information about you during your use of the Site, such as the server your computer is logged onto (i.e., your IP address) and your browser type (for example, FireFox or Internet Explorer). Future Students may use this information for its internal business purposes but will not sell, share with, or rent this information to any third outside. This information will not be used by Future Students to contact or identify any person individually.

The Site may contain links to other websites. Such websites may use cookies and/or other data collection tools. Future Students is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or content of such other websites.

###### Dealings with Customers

We may also collect personal information from our customers from time to time, such as their name, address, and contact details when we communicate with them in person, over the phone, in emails, or otherwise. In some circumstances we may collect customers’ personal information from a third party who is dealing with us on the customers’ behalf.

We will only use customers’ personal information to provide them with assistance or services they have requested, to operate our business, or as otherwise permitted by law.

Future Students may from time to time send existing customers information and marketing materials relating to the business. Future Students will obide by Australian laws relating to the use of electronic messages (email, SMS, MMS and instant messaging), telephone and faxes for marketing purposes, including the ability for recipients to ‘opt-out’ from receiving such messages at any time.

## 2\. THE SERVICES

###### Overview of Future Students’ Services

Future Students collects information about the website(s) that you visit and the advertisements that you see while online via Future Students’ technology provider (the “Technology”). You may encounter the Technology when:

  * Future Students or one of our Advertisers displays online advertisements on a website that you visit;
  * when you open an email that contains an advertisement placed by Future Students or one of our Advertisers; and/or
  * when one of the Advertisers places one of Future Students’ web beacons on a website that you visit.

We use the information collected by the Technology in order to help make the Advertisements you see more relevant to you, and for Advertisement delivery and reporting purposes.

###### Information Collected via the Services

The Technology collects and uses information regarding your interaction with the Services, including, without limitation, the IP address used to access the Internet, the type of browser used, which and how many Advertiser webpages have been viewed, search terms entered on Advertiser websites, referral URLs, and the date and time of website visits.

Future Students uses this information to analyse trends, identify the audience most likely to respond to an advertisement and to tailor advertisement placements for Future Students’ Advertisers accordingly. This information may be shared with third parties (see the “Disclosure of Information to Third Parties” section below). This information will not be used by Future Students to contact or identify any person individually.

###### Cookies and Web Beacons

Future Students uses cookies and web beacons in connection with the Technology. These cookies and web beacons are served by our existing and future technology partners, including but not limited to Brandscreen, TubeMogul, Doubleclick(Google), Turn and Adap.TV, Appnexus, Mediamath etc.. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. Certain cookies, persistent cookies, remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. You can also remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. Cookies help Future Students better understand the effectiveness of a Future Students Advertisement (for example, by tracking the way in which you may respond to, and interact with, a Future Students Advertisement, or the location and context in which you view a Future Students Advertisement). Future Students’ cookies may also help control the number of times you view a Future Students Advertisement.

Web beacons (also known as “1X1 pixels” or “clear GIFs”) are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a webpage or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. Future Students also uses web beacons, in combination with cookies, to analyse usage patterns. The use of a web beacon allows Future Students to record when you have visited a particular webpage or interacted with a certain email, along with additional information that the website or email may choose to include with the beacon.

###### Third Party Links and Websites

Advertisements may contain links to other websites, including those of the Advertisers and our contractors and affiliates. Such websites may use cookies and/or other data collection tools. Future Students is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or the content of such websites. Future Students encourages everyone to read the posted privacy policies whenever interacting with any website to learn more about the privacy practices of that website. Future Students has no control over the use of any information by third party websites, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any information. Similarly, Future Students does not have access to, or control of, the cookies and/or other data collection tools that may be placed on any advertisement by a third-party, including those of the Advertisers, and this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies and/or other data collection tools by any third party other than in connection with the Site and the Services.

###### Storage of Information

We retain the information collected via the Technology in order to ensure that the Technology is functioning properly. From the outset this information is anonymous and is stored indefinitely.

###### Opting out

If you would like to opt-out from having Future Students collect your information in connection with the Site and the Technology, please click each of the following links below and follow the opt out instructions of our technology partners :

Brandscreen at <http://www.brandscreen.com/Privacy.aspx>

TubeMogul at <http://www.tubemogul.com/company/privacy/>

Turn at <http://www.turn.com/privacy/optout/>

Mediamath at <http://www.mediamath.com/privacy/>

Google at <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>

AppNexus at <http://www.appnexus.com/platform-policy>

If you would like to opt-out from having Future Students’ partners collect your information in connection with the Site and the Technology, you may control your privacy settings using the DAA and NAI Opt-out links below, which allow consumers to not participate in the behavioural advertising delivered by DAA and NAI member companies, respectively:

Cookies will need to be enabled when you visit the opt-out site as when you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie tells us not to collect your information to tailor Advertisements to your interests. Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you will need to renew your opt-out choice or adjust your browser settings to allow the opt-out cookie to be effective.

You may also have the option to view your profile, edit it or opt-out of receiving targeted ads, on websites operated by companies who are signatories of the Australian Guidelines for Third party On-line Behavioural Advertising. You can find out more information about your options at [www.youronlinechoices.com.au](http://www.youronlinechoices.com.au/).

## 3\. GENERAL (APPLICABLE TO THE SITE AND THE SERVICES)

###### Information Security

Future Students has implemented reasonable security measures in order to protect information from loss, misuse and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and make no warranty as to security. If you have any questions about our security practices, please send an email to us at [custcare@futurestudents.com](mailto:custcare@futurestudents.com).

###### Information Relating to Children

Our products and services are designed for those 13 years of age and older. We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under the age of 13. If we are made aware that we have received personal information from someone under 13, we will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our records.

###### Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

We may share information collected via the Technology with Advertisers or other contractors or technology vendors in connection with the Services. Similarly, we may enhance the information collected via the Technology with information collected from Advertisers or other ad networks. This information will not be used by Future Students to contact or identify any person individually.

We may also disclose information about our customers or individuals who use the Services to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so for legal compliance purposes and as described in the “Assignability” section below. For purposes of the preceding sentence, “legal compliance purposes” includes, without limitation, compliance with laws, cooperation with any governmental and self-regulatory investigations, and disclosure whenever Future Students believes disclosure is necessary to limit its legal liability or to protect or enforce the rights, interests, or safety of the Site, our users or any third party.

###### Assignability

If all or part of Future Students is sold, merged or otherwise transferred to another entity or undergoes any other corporate change or restructuring, whatever form it may take, your personal information or other information may be transferred as part of that transaction.

###### Data Collection Is In Australia

The Site and Services are operated from Australia. If you are located outside of Australia, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be collected within Australia. By using our Site and/or participating in any of our Services, you consent to this transfer.

Information collected about you from the Site may be transferred to Future Students’ related offices and technology partners in the United States, India, Japan, Europe and New Zealand. By visiting the Site, you consent to this transfer.

###### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is subject to change. If we make any material or substantive changes in the way that we use data, we will post a conspicuous notice of those changes on the Site and in this privacy policy.

###### Complaints

Please let us know if you have any concerns or complaints about how we have handled your personal information. If we receive a complaint, we will contact you as soon as possible to discuss this with you. Future Students takes your privacy seriously and will work with you to address any concerns you have.

###### Contact Information

Please contact us if you have any queries about the personal information that we hold about you or the way we handle that personal information. Our contact details for privacy queries are set out below.

##### Customer Care  
Future Students Pty Ltd  
Mail: Suite 501, Level 5, Grafton Bond Building, 201 Kent St  
Email: [custcare@futurestudents.com](mailto:custcare@futurestudents.com)  
Telephone: +61 (2) 8203 5921
